driving is a serious business
in western australia careless driving
carries a maximum penalty of 12
units or 600 furthermore the offence of
careless driving causing
death grievous bodily harm or bodily
harm
carries a maximum penalty of
imprisonment for three years
or a fine of 36 000 as well as the loss
of your driver's license
if you are a probationary driver your
license will be cancelled
careless driving means operating a
vehicle without due care or attention
and can often be the result of an
innocent lapse of attention
or concentration although careless
driving is a different offence to
dangerous or reckless driving
it still carries serious consequences
situations of careless driving may
include
missing a stop sign your vehicle moving
across a double line
or taking your eyes off the road to talk
to a passenger
so don't risk the serious penalties that
may apply
speak to an experienced traffic lawyer
such as
andrew williams today